Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Fierce Battle against the Giant Beast
Episode 5
According to the description of the residents, the monster is in this direction
Then it can only pass through this bridge when entering the city.
Lay a trap first to stop the monster from advancing
Wolffy used to be the best at digging holes when he was catching goats.
Wolffy is not here, I’m a bit unaccustomed to it
Wolffy where are you?
Everyone, be careful tonight
what sound
Is it the monster?
Maybe we were too nervous and heard wrongly
Let’s go
So dangerous
Scared me to death
It looks like it will be very dangerous in the city tonight. What should I do?
Then we need to find Weslie quickly.
Just wait for me
Nephew, it’s dangerous outside tonight.
I have arranged for the residents to hide in the palace. You don’t have to worry.
Hope you can spend this evening safely
Thank you for your hard work, Uncle
nephew
Have a good rest
We searched every room
Only this room has never been searched
What’s going on?
In, in, in a word
Your friend won’t be here anymore
Let’s look elsewhere
There should be some rooms that I haven’t found yet.
Weslie
are you there
Who are you
Someone is coming
Don’t fight
it’s you
Look at my entanglement attack
Stop fighting. Stop fighting.
Don’t fight
Long time no see Sparky
Your name is Sparky
So what? Do you still want to fight?
The amount of information today is a bit overwhelming. Let me catch my breath for a moment.
There’s someone here named Weslie and there’s someone named Sparky
Then is there someone named Wolffy?
What do you want to do by breaking into the palace at night?
I came in here to find my friend Weslie
It’s not you Weslie of Bulala, it’s another one
Believe it or not, I didn’t destroy Bulala.
So you were looking for him
He has left the palace
It’s too dangerous for him to be out there if he encounters a monster
this monster
Isn’t it the one that attacked me in the cave?
Successful
not good
The monster is coming
What should we do? The monster is going to eat us.
Who will save us?
The monster is coming
Most of the residents have taken refuge in the palace, right?
The guy who destroyed Bulala is still out there.
What? does he really want to stop the monster from destroying?
Yeah, it’s simply overestimating his abilities.
Weslie
He is fighting the monster
What
No, I have to help him
Wait, the monster is very dangerous
His fangs and claws will scratch you.
It’s because of the danger that I went to help him.
Let go
No, I won’t let go
I have to help Weslie
Don’t go
You also want to hinder me
Don’t get me wrong
I’ll go with you
The monster is out there destroying our homes.
And as the prince of the Bulala people, how can I stand idly by?
wait for me
If this continues, the city will be destroyed.
Give it back to you
Try this trick
Successful
Do you like the gloves I made for you?
Very suitable
Too bad
I found you
You still can’t do it without me, Weslie
Wolffy
It’s me
you
How did you become like this?
Ouch, ouch
It’s a long story
Get out of the way
Wolffy
pull together
are you okay
I, Wolffy, don’t fall down that easily.
it hurts
Stop talking. The monster is gone.
Where did the monster go?
Run quickly
The monster is gone
Are all people named Weslie so awesome?
It’s your friends who are more powerful
It was you who saved us just now
Why is this happening?
My house was smashed
OMG
my home is gone
Sorry, I underestimated the monster
To be continued